[{"answer": "You kiddin? Who else would hack through that place or that place at night", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'll work anywhere, anytime. I know I can't be choosy", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Alright, forget it if you're not going to be serious", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Just what", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Truck drivers bring up that place Specials that blow up in your hand. But this guy don't deal no shit. Just quality. If you ever need anything, I can put you in touch", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "For a fee", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Try holding the match like this", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " This I gotta see", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "As I said, he isn't Italian. Besides, I thought they just killed them", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Why don't they leave a pidgeon instead of a canary", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Don't be naive. They can't kill everybody. They have different punishments for different things. Like, if they kill a stool pidgeon, they leave a canary on the body. It's symbolic", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't know. Maybe they don't leave a canary. Don't be technical. What I'm saying is if this newsstand guy's Italian and his fingers are gone, maybe he's a thief", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " if you talk to my friend, he'll assign you to something", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Well, we're all working tonight", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, I just, you know..", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Real down", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Like do anything, you know", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It's easy to remember.  Easy Lay", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't like my real name", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What's your real name", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " What's your real name", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You tried to run away in my taxi but your friend", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It don't matter.  I'm gonna get you outta here.", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't remember", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "We better make it, or Sport'll get mad.  How do you want to make it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It don't matter.  I'm gonna get you outta here.", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " I don't want to make it.  I came here to get you out", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "We better make it, or Sport'll get mad.  How do you want to make it", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You want to make it like this?", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Can't you listen to me?  Don't you want to get out of here", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " But you're the one that wanted to get away.  You're the one that came into my cab", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Fuck it!  Fuck it!  Fuck it!  Fuck it!  Fuck it!  Fuck it!  Fuck it", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Don't you understand anything", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Where", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I ain't ever been there, but it don't seem like such a bad place", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You just gonna leave 'em", "docId": "Taxi-Driver.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Cops don't do nothin", "qsentId": 38}]